123indianonline.com 2008-12-18

# Tamil Movie Online | Privacy Policy | 123IndianOnline

## Privacy Policy

**123IndianOnline** Online Privacy Policy (last updated APRIL 18, 2008) 

**123IndianOnline** has established this Privacy Policy to explain how it protects and manages the personal information that it collects from you (the customer) online. 

## Our Commitment To Privacy:

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

## The Information We Collect:

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our ezine or newsletter as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. 

For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

## The Way We Use Information:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the **123IndianOnline** website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. 

## Cookies and Google Advertising

Third parties, such as Google AdSense, may place and read cookies on your browser, or use web beacons to collect information, while serving ads on **123IndianOnline**. Here is how Google explains cookies: �A �cookie� is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies.�

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies. 

## Our Commitment To Data Security:

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

## Our Commitment To Children�s Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website/blog is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

## How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections 

## Contact Information

Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to support@icanearn.com for further clarification.

This privacy policy was created by [ICanEarn.](http://www.icanearn.com/)
